

Profile

I'm a full senior stack developer with the goal of making the world a little better. I look forward to sharing my knowledge and learning new ideas.

Disclaimer

Some information has been removed from this particular online version. Please send me an email to request the full ${\sf CV}$

Employment History

Senior Full Stack Developer, Omda, Solna

MAY 2024 - PRESENT

Designing digital archives, web applications, phone applications, and container runtime environments for hospitals in different countries

Full Stack Developer, Omda, Solna

AUGUST 2021 - MAY 2024

Clustered system development for hospitals of different countries

Software Developer, Reynolds Packaging, Green Bay

MAY 2020 - DECEMBER 2020

Development of software in Java and C for data logging and monitoring of industrial machines.

Education

Computer Science, University of Wisconsin - Green Bay, Green Bay

SEPTEMBER 2017 - MAY 2021

GPA: 3.73 / 4.00

Major Computer Science - Minor Mathematics

Courses

Software Engineering, University of Wisconsin - Green Bay

Artificial Intelligence, University of Wisconsin - Green Bay

Theory of Algorithms, University of Wisconsin - Green Bay

Complete transcript available upon request

Details

vicfor002@gmail.com

DRIVING LICENSE

AM/B

DATE OF BIRTH

1996-11-22

Links

Website

<u>Linkedin</u>

GitHub

Skills

Scala

Angular

Cassandra

Java

Docker

GO

C#

Python

SQL

Linux

Languages

Swedish

English

German